[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "If 950 ml is added to 950 ml of a 2 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "If 800 ml is added to 400 ml of a 30 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "If 2300 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 27 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "If 2800 ml is added to 700 ml of a 2.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "If 50 ml is added to 50 ml of a 4 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "If 2700 ml is added to 900 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 50 ml of a 7.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 400 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "If 3400 ml is added to 850 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 150 ml of a 30 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "If 5000 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 32.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 150 ml of a 22.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "If 400 ml is added to 400 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 350 ml of a 4.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "If 500 ml is added to 500 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "If 1400 ml is added to 700 ml of a 28.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "If 2250 ml is added to 750 ml of a 4 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "If 150 ml is added to 150 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "If 3800 ml is added to 950 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "If 100 ml is added to 50 ml of a 7.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "If 2700 ml is added to 900 ml of a 4 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 200 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "If 50 ml is added to 50 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "If 1100 ml is added to 550 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 26,
    "Question": "If 4400 ml is added to 1100 ml of a 25 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 27,
    "Question": "If 1600 ml is added to 400 ml of a 47.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 28,
    "Question": "If 2000 ml is added to 500 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 29,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 450 ml of a 17 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 30,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 450 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 31,
    "Question": "If 2200 ml is added to 550 ml of a 45 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 32,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 700 ml of a 5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 33,
    "Question": "If 1050 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 12 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 34,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 12 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 35,
    "Question": "If 1000 ml is added to 1000 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 36,
    "Question": "If 1400 ml is added to 700 ml of a 4.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 37,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 38,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 300 ml of a 27 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 39,
    "Question": "If 3400 ml is added to 850 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 40,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 150 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 41,
    "Question": "If 3800 ml is added to 950 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 42,
    "Question": "If 400 ml is added to 200 ml of a 19.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 43,
    "Question": "If 1400 ml is added to 350 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 44,
    "Question": "If 300 ml is added to 300 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 45,
    "Question": "If 1800 ml is added to 450 ml of a 27.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 46,
    "Question": "If 250 ml is added to 250 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 47,
    "Question": "If 2800 ml is added to 700 ml of a 5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 48,
    "Question": "If 2250 ml is added to 750 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 49,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 450 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 50,
    "Question": "If 800 ml is added to 800 ml of a 12 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 51,
    "Question": "If 1800 ml is added to 450 ml of a 37.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 52,
    "Question": "If 1800 ml is added to 450 ml of a 45 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 53,
    "Question": "If 3400 ml is added to 850 ml of a 27.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 54,
    "Question": "If 1650 ml is added to 550 ml of a 40 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 55,
    "Question": "If 1250 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 56,
    "Question": "If 1000 ml is added to 500 ml of a 24 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 57,
    "Question": "If 2000 ml is added to 1000 ml of a 9 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 58,
    "Question": "If 2300 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 25.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 59,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 40 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 60,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 200 ml of a 12 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 61,
    "Question": "If 1900 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 62,
    "Question": "If 2400 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 63,
    "Question": "If 4600 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 64,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 200 ml of a 11 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 65,
    "Question": "If 1500 ml is added to 500 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 66,
    "Question": "If 3750 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 67,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 300 ml of a 45 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 68,
    "Question": "If 1600 ml is added to 400 ml of a 27.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 69,
    "Question": "If 250 ml is added to 250 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 70,
    "Question": "If 800 ml is added to 800 ml of a 13 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 71,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 350 ml of a 27 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 72,
    "Question": "If 3400 ml is added to 850 ml of a 40 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 73,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 600 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 74,
    "Question": "If 2250 ml is added to 750 ml of a 34 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 8.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 75,
    "Question": "If 100 ml is added to 50 ml of a 28.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 76,
    "Question": "If 1050 ml is added to 350 ml of a 38 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 77,
    "Question": "If 2400 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 10.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 78,
    "Question": "If 2700 ml is added to 900 ml of a 6 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 79,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 80,
    "Question": "If 150 ml is added to 50 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 81,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 24 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 82,
    "Question": "If 5000 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 25 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 83,
    "Question": "If 50 ml is added to 50 ml of a 9 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 84,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 100 ml of a 28.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 85,
    "Question": "If 4800 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 86,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 600 ml of a 4.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 87,
    "Question": "If 750 ml is added to 750 ml of a 20 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 88,
    "Question": "If 1500 ml is added to 750 ml of a 30 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 89,
    "Question": "If 800 ml is added to 400 ml of a 30 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 90,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 100 ml of a 27 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 91,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 92,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 4 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 93,
    "Question": "If 3000 ml is added to 750 ml of a 12.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 94,
    "Question": "If 2200 ml is added to 1100 ml of a 19.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 6.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 95,
    "Question": "If 1050 ml is added to 350 ml of a 2 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 96,
    "Question": "If 400 ml is added to 100 ml of a 27.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 97,
    "Question": "If 450 ml is added to 150 ml of a 30 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 7.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 98,
    "Question": "If 1400 ml is added to 350 ml of a 12.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 2.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 99,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 50 ml of a 47.5 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 9.5,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 100,
    "Question": "If 2000 ml is added to 500 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, what is the new strength in %w/v?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "%w/v"
  },
  {
    "Number": 101,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 600 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 102,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 150 ml of a 1 in 700 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 103,
    "Question": "If 550 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 104,
    "Question": "If 2800 ml is added to 700 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 105,
    "Question": "If 4800 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 106,
    "Question": "If 1500 ml is added to 500 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 107,
    "Question": "If 1700 ml is added to 850 ml of a 1 in 750 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 108,
    "Question": "If 1600 ml is added to 800 ml of a 1 in 750 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 109,
    "Question": "If 2200 ml is added to 1100 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2550,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 110,
    "Question": "If 2500 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2850,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 111,
    "Question": "If 300 ml is added to 100 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 112,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 150 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 113,
    "Question": "If 3800 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 350 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1750,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 114,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2550,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 115,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 200 ml of a 1 in 100 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 116,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 300 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 4000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 117,
    "Question": "If 1800 ml is added to 450 ml of a 1 in 200 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 118,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 200 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 119,
    "Question": "If 1400 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 120,
    "Question": "If 1350 ml is added to 450 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 121,
    "Question": "If 500 ml is added to 500 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1900,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 122,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 700 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 123,
    "Question": "If 250 ml is added to 250 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1300,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 124,
    "Question": "If 3800 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 125,
    "Question": "If 1900 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 126,
    "Question": "If 1100 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1950,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 127,
    "Question": "If 2400 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 128,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 600 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2850,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 129,
    "Question": "If 2300 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 130,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 131,
    "Question": "If 2500 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1650,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 132,
    "Question": "If 3750 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 1 in 50 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 133,
    "Question": "If 2550 ml is added to 850 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 4000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 134,
    "Question": "If 500 ml is added to 250 ml of a 1 in 750 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 135,
    "Question": "If 4400 ml is added to 1100 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 136,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 50 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 5000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 137,
    "Question": "If 3200 ml is added to 800 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 138,
    "Question": "If 400 ml is added to 100 ml of a 1 in 150 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 750,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 139,
    "Question": "If 1600 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 450 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 140,
    "Question": "If 700 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1650,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 141,
    "Question": "If 350 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 142,
    "Question": "If 900 ml is added to 900 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 143,
    "Question": "If 300 ml is added to 100 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 144,
    "Question": "If 4000 ml is added to 1000 ml of a 1 in 450 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 145,
    "Question": "If 800 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2550,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 146,
    "Question": "If 1300 ml is added to 650 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 147,
    "Question": "If 3750 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 148,
    "Question": "If 2550 ml is added to 850 ml of a 1 in 750 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 149,
    "Question": "If 2100 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 150,
    "Question": "If 3750 ml is added to 1250 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 151,
    "Question": "If 4600 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 1 in 200 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 152,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 150 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 153,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 100 ml of a 1 in 200 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 154,
    "Question": "If 300 ml is added to 100 ml of a 1 in 300 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 155,
    "Question": "If 350 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 156,
    "Question": "If 150 ml is added to 150 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 157,
    "Question": "If 1150 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 1 in 450 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 158,
    "Question": "If 2700 ml is added to 900 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 159,
    "Question": "If 3200 ml is added to 800 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2750,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 160,
    "Question": "If 2100 ml is added to 700 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 161,
    "Question": "If 900 ml is added to 900 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 162,
    "Question": "If 2100 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 900 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2700,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 163,
    "Question": "If 200 ml is added to 50 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 4250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 164,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 1 in 700 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 165,
    "Question": "If 2700 ml is added to 900 ml of a 1 in 300 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 166,
    "Question": "If 3150 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 50 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 167,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 150 ml of a 1 in 100 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 168,
    "Question": "If 2200 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 4250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 169,
    "Question": "If 3600 ml is added to 1200 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 170,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 300 ml of a 1 in 550 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2750,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 171,
    "Question": "If 2600 ml is added to 650 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 172,
    "Question": "If 1650 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 350 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 173,
    "Question": "If 900 ml is added to 450 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 174,
    "Question": "If 650 ml is added to 650 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 175,
    "Question": "If 350 ml is added to 350 ml of a 1 in 700 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 176,
    "Question": "If 1050 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1300,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 177,
    "Question": "If 1050 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 178,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 600 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 179,
    "Question": "If 1700 ml is added to 850 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2550,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 180,
    "Question": "If 1650 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 150 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 181,
    "Question": "If 600 ml is added to 300 ml of a 1 in 650 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1950,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 182,
    "Question": "If 1800 ml is added to 900 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2850,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 183,
    "Question": "If 150 ml is added to 50 ml of a 1 in 850 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 184,
    "Question": "If 1600 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 900 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 4500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 185,
    "Question": "If 2850 ml is added to 950 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 186,
    "Question": "If 900 ml is added to 300 ml of a 1 in 950 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 187,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 150 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 188,
    "Question": "If 1350 ml is added to 450 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 3200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 189,
    "Question": "If 2000 ml is added to 500 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 190,
    "Question": "If 4600 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 1 in 350 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1750,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 191,
    "Question": "If 1200 ml is added to 400 ml of a 1 in 300 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1200,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 192,
    "Question": "If 300 ml is added to 300 ml of a 1 in 400 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 193,
    "Question": "If 50 ml is added to 50 ml of a 1 in 350 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 700,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 194,
    "Question": "If 4000 ml is added to 1000 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 1250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 195,
    "Question": "If 4600 ml is added to 1150 ml of a 1 in 500 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 196,
    "Question": "If 3200 ml is added to 800 ml of a 1 in 450 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2250,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 197,
    "Question": "If 2400 ml is added to 800 ml of a 1 in 700 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2800,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 198,
    "Question": "If 750 ml is added to 750 ml of a 1 in 250 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 199,
    "Question": "If 2100 ml is added to 1050 ml of a 1 in 800 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2400,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 200,
    "Question": "If 1100 ml is added to 550 ml of a 1 in 900 solution, what is the new strength in parts? For 1 in X, just enter the numerical value of X in the answer box.",
    "Answer": 2700,
    "Units": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 201,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 10.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 21 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 202,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 72 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 203,
    "Question": "If you want to make 560 ml of a 7 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 204,
    "Question": "If you want to make 60 ml of a 0.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 1.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 205,
    "Question": "If you want to make 580 ml of a 1 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 4 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 206,
    "Question": "If you want to make 120 ml of a 8.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 207,
    "Question": "If you want to make 10 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 19 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 208,
    "Question": "If you want to make 850 ml of a 6 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 209,
    "Question": "If you want to make 260 ml of a 6.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 210,
    "Question": "If you want to make 15 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 211,
    "Question": "If you want to make 120 ml of a 17 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 68 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 212,
    "Question": "If you want to make 230 ml of a 13 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 115,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 213,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 13.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 214,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 17 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 85 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 215,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 14.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 43.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 216,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 3.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 7 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 217,
    "Question": "If you want to make 540 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 48 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 218,
    "Question": "If you want to make 330 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 48 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 219,
    "Question": "If you want to make 105 ml of a 16.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 49.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 220,
    "Question": "If you want to make 675 ml of a 6 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 221,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 222,
    "Question": "If you want to make 300 ml of a 7.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 223,
    "Question": "If you want to make 130 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 20 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 224,
    "Question": "If you want to make 140 ml of a 8.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 225,
    "Question": "If you want to make 75 ml of a 13.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 40.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 226,
    "Question": "If you want to make 275 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 70 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 227,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 228,
    "Question": "If you want to make 475 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 47.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 229,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 230,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 18.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 55.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 231,
    "Question": "If you want to make 300 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 15 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 232,
    "Question": "If you want to make 600 ml of a 17 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 51 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 233,
    "Question": "If you want to make 435 ml of a 6 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 18 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 234,
    "Question": "If you want to make 405 ml of a 18.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 55.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 235,
    "Question": "If you want to make 560 ml of a 3.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 14 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 236,
    "Question": "If you want to make 75 ml of a 6.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 19.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 237,
    "Question": "If you want to make 800 ml of a 6.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 238,
    "Question": "If you want to make 800 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 38 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 239,
    "Question": "If you want to make 60 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 12 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 240,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 14 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 241,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 11 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 44 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 242,
    "Question": "If you want to make 425 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 50 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 243,
    "Question": "If you want to make 500 ml of a 14.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 72.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 244,
    "Question": "If you want to make 80 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 38 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 245,
    "Question": "If you want to make 130 ml of a 13.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 246,
    "Question": "If you want to make 220 ml of a 13 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 247,
    "Question": "If you want to make 345 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 45 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 115,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 248,
    "Question": "If you want to make 500 ml of a 1.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 7.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 249,
    "Question": "If you want to make 390 ml of a 12.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 37.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 250,
    "Question": "If you want to make 195 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 9 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 251,
    "Question": "If you want to make 495 ml of a 16 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 48 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 165,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 252,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 18.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 55.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 253,
    "Question": "If you want to make 540 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 254,
    "Question": "If you want to make 405 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 255,
    "Question": "If you want to make 195 ml of a 7 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 21 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 256,
    "Question": "If you want to make 540 ml of a 1.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 4.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 257,
    "Question": "If you want to make 285 ml of a 18 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 54 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 258,
    "Question": "If you want to make 320 ml of a 2 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 4 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 259,
    "Question": "If you want to make 740 ml of a 15 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 60 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 185,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 260,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 3.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 14 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 261,
    "Question": "If you want to make 540 ml of a 19 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 57 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 262,
    "Question": "If you want to make 20 ml of a 0.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 2 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 263,
    "Question": "If you want to make 570 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 190,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 264,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 47.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 265,
    "Question": "If you want to make 800 ml of a 7 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 35 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 266,
    "Question": "If you want to make 275 ml of a 10 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 50 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 267,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 5.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 268,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 15.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 62 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 269,
    "Question": "If you want to make 320 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 19 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 270,
    "Question": "If you want to make 330 ml of a 14.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 29 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 165,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 271,
    "Question": "If you want to make 600 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 40 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 272,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 11 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 22 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 273,
    "Question": "If you want to make 220 ml of a 18.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 37 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 274,
    "Question": "If you want to make 280 ml of a 3.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 7 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 275,
    "Question": "If you want to make 225 ml of a 17.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 276,
    "Question": "If you want to make 340 ml of a 16.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 33 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 277,
    "Question": "If you want to make 550 ml of a 0.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 2.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 278,
    "Question": "If you want to make 280 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 279,
    "Question": "If you want to make 80 ml of a 6.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 280,
    "Question": "If you want to make 440 ml of a 1.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 281,
    "Question": "If you want to make 555 ml of a 3 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 9 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 185,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 282,
    "Question": "If you want to make 125 ml of a 5.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 283,
    "Question": "If you want to make 700 ml of a 11 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 44 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 284,
    "Question": "If you want to make 425 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 47.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 285,
    "Question": "If you want to make 775 ml of a 7 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 35 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 155,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 286,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 7.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 37.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 287,
    "Question": "If you want to make 40 ml of a 18.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 37 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 288,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 14.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 72.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 289,
    "Question": "If you want to make 360 ml of a 12.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 25 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 290,
    "Question": "If you want to make 440 ml of a 15.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 62 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 291,
    "Question": "If you want to make 290 ml of a 9.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 19 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 292,
    "Question": "If you want to make 520 ml of a 7 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 293,
    "Question": "If you want to make 480 ml of a 2.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 7.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 294,
    "Question": "If you want to make 780 ml of a 8.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 195,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 295,
    "Question": "If you want to make 90 ml of a 0.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 1.5 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 296,
    "Question": "If you want to make 800 ml of a 2.5 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 10 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 297,
    "Question": "If you want to make 390 ml of a 12 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 195,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 298,
    "Question": "If you want to make 495 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 165,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 299,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 8 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 40 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 300,
    "Question": "If you want to make 125 ml of a 19 %w/v solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 95 %w/v solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 301,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 6 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 30 M solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 302,
    "Question": "If you want to make 90 ml of a 13.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 303,
    "Question": "If you want to make 260 ml of a 16.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 33 M solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 304,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 16.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 82.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 305,
    "Question": "If you want to make 220 ml of a 3 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 M solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 306,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 10.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 21 M solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 307,
    "Question": "If you want to make 320 ml of a 5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 20 M solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 308,
    "Question": "If you want to make 570 ml of a 16 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 48 M solution?",
    "Answer": 190,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 309,
    "Question": "If you want to make 480 ml of a 17.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 310,
    "Question": "If you want to make 465 ml of a 8 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 M solution?",
    "Answer": 155,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 311,
    "Question": "If you want to make 375 ml of a 14.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 43.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 312,
    "Question": "If you want to make 725 ml of a 4.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 22.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 313,
    "Question": "If you want to make 180 ml of a 10 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 40 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 314,
    "Question": "If you want to make 80 ml of a 6.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 M solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 315,
    "Question": "If you want to make 15 ml of a 11.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 316,
    "Question": "If you want to make 175 ml of a 3.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 17.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 317,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 13 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 M solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 318,
    "Question": "If you want to make 325 ml of a 9.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 47.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 319,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 7 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 35 M solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 320,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 321,
    "Question": "If you want to make 750 ml of a 3.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 17.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 322,
    "Question": "If you want to make 60 ml of a 14 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 M solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 323,
    "Question": "If you want to make 280 ml of a 14 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 M solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 324,
    "Question": "If you want to make 80 ml of a 17 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 M solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 325,
    "Question": "If you want to make 375 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 326,
    "Question": "If you want to make 310 ml of a 12 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 M solution?",
    "Answer": 155,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 327,
    "Question": "If you want to make 180 ml of a 17 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 68 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 328,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 13.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27 M solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 329,
    "Question": "If you want to make 435 ml of a 14.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 43.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 330,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 15 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 331,
    "Question": "If you want to make 555 ml of a 2 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 M solution?",
    "Answer": 185,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 332,
    "Question": "If you want to make 420 ml of a 17.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 70 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 333,
    "Question": "If you want to make 680 ml of a 5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 20 M solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 334,
    "Question": "If you want to make 30 ml of a 0.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 1.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 335,
    "Question": "If you want to make 435 ml of a 8 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 24 M solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 336,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 6.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 32.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 337,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 9 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 45 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 338,
    "Question": "If you want to make 140 ml of a 3 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 12 M solution?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 339,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 8.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 M solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 340,
    "Question": "If you want to make 25 ml of a 14 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 70 M solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 341,
    "Question": "If you want to make 425 ml of a 10 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 50 M solution?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 342,
    "Question": "If you want to make 30 ml of a 12.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 25 M solution?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 343,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 11 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 22 M solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 344,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 16.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 33 M solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 345,
    "Question": "If you want to make 425 ml of a 14.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 72.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 346,
    "Question": "If you want to make 405 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 3 M solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 347,
    "Question": "If you want to make 240 ml of a 15.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 46.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 348,
    "Question": "If you want to make 210 ml of a 14 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 349,
    "Question": "If you want to make 680 ml of a 2.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 10 M solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 350,
    "Question": "If you want to make 210 ml of a 5.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 16.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 351,
    "Question": "If you want to make 600 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 3 M solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 352,
    "Question": "If you want to make 390 ml of a 4.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 13.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 353,
    "Question": "If you want to make 60 ml of a 3 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 12 M solution?",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 354,
    "Question": "If you want to make 680 ml of a 10.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 42 M solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 355,
    "Question": "If you want to make 720 ml of a 9 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 36 M solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 356,
    "Question": "If you want to make 375 ml of a 7.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 37.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 357,
    "Question": "If you want to make 20 ml of a 13 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 M solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 358,
    "Question": "If you want to make 360 ml of a 1.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 359,
    "Question": "If you want to make 135 ml of a 16.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 49.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 360,
    "Question": "If you want to make 180 ml of a 13.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 361,
    "Question": "If you want to make 260 ml of a 14.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 29 M solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 362,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 17 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 34 M solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 363,
    "Question": "If you want to make 435 ml of a 16 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 48 M solution?",
    "Answer": 145,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 364,
    "Question": "If you want to make 440 ml of a 6.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 26 M solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 365,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 10 M solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 366,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 3 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 15 M solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 367,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 11 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 22 M solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 368,
    "Question": "If you want to make 720 ml of a 0.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 2 M solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 369,
    "Question": "If you want to make 975 ml of a 8 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 40 M solution?",
    "Answer": 195,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 370,
    "Question": "If you want to make 80 ml of a 13.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 54 M solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 371,
    "Question": "If you want to make 180 ml of a 3.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 14 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 372,
    "Question": "If you want to make 125 ml of a 17 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 85 M solution?",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 373,
    "Question": "If you want to make 450 ml of a 5.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 27.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 374,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 16 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 32 M solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 375,
    "Question": "If you want to make 540 ml of a 13 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52 M solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 376,
    "Question": "If you want to make 210 ml of a 12.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 25 M solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 377,
    "Question": "If you want to make 350 ml of a 3 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 15 M solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 378,
    "Question": "If you want to make 475 ml of a 11.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 57.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 379,
    "Question": "If you want to make 360 ml of a 18.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 74 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 380,
    "Question": "If you want to make 390 ml of a 1.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 4.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 381,
    "Question": "If you want to make 480 ml of a 15.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 46.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 382,
    "Question": "If you want to make 310 ml of a 6 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 12 M solution?",
    "Answer": 155,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 383,
    "Question": "If you want to make 525 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 3 M solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 384,
    "Question": "If you want to make 480 ml of a 5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 20 M solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 385,
    "Question": "If you want to make 740 ml of a 4.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 18 M solution?",
    "Answer": 185,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 386,
    "Question": "If you want to make 200 ml of a 1.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 6 M solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 387,
    "Question": "If you want to make 480 ml of a 12 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 36 M solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 388,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 1 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 4 M solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 389,
    "Question": "If you want to make 875 ml of a 10.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 52.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 390,
    "Question": "If you want to make 100 ml of a 9 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 18 M solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 391,
    "Question": "If you want to make 220 ml of a 9.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 38 M solution?",
    "Answer": 55,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 392,
    "Question": "If you want to make 225 ml of a 15 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 75 M solution?",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 393,
    "Question": "If you want to make 250 ml of a 8.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 17 M solution?",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 394,
    "Question": "If you want to make 400 ml of a 16 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 32 M solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 395,
    "Question": "If you want to make 170 ml of a 12.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 25 M solution?",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 396,
    "Question": "If you want to make 220 ml of a 14 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 28 M solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 397,
    "Question": "If you want to make 250 ml of a 18 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 90 M solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 398,
    "Question": "If you want to make 375 ml of a 12 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 36 M solution?",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 399,
    "Question": "If you want to make 330 ml of a 14.5 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 43.5 M solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 400,
    "Question": "If you want to make 270 ml of a 18 M solution, how much would you need to take from a stock that is a 54 M solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 401,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 270 ml of a 1 in 900 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 402,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 80 ml of a 1 in 900 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 403,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 240 ml of a 1 in 525 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 404,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 300 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 405,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 840 ml of a 1 in 300 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 406,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 150 ml of a 1 in 525 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 407,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 350 ml of a 1 in 350 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 408,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 450 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 409,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 1600 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 410,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 500 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 411,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 60 ml of a 1 in 150 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 412,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 640 ml of a 1 in 600 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 413,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 270 ml of a 1 in 675 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 414,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 100 ml of a 1 in 750 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 415,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 80 ml of a 1 in 1400 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 416,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 300 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 417,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 320 ml of a 1 in 800 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 418,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 550 ml of a 1 in 1100 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 419,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 330 ml of a 1 in 1375 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 420,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 3000 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 421,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 210 ml of a 1 in 675 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 422,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 180 ml of a 1 in 900 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 423,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 140 ml of a 1 in 500 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 424,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 420 ml of a 1 in 1575 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 425,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 660 ml of a 1 in 275 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 426,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 70 ml of a 1 in 175 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 427,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 225 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 428,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 450 ml of a 1 in 1250 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 429,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 140 ml of a 1 in 1575 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 430,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 100 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 431,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 600 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 432,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 1080 ml of a 1 in 1800 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 433,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 840 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 434,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 80 ml of a 1 in 700 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 435,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 480 ml of a 1 in 2100 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 436,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 240 ml of a 1 in 750 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 437,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 140 ml of a 1 in 1575 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 438,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 120 ml of a 1 in 350 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 439,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 480 ml of a 1 in 200 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 440,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 280 ml of a 1 in 100 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 441,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 540 ml of a 1 in 600 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 442,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 490 ml of a 1 in 1575 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 443,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 400 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 444,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 1200 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 445,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 350 ml of a 1 in 500 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 446,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 500 ml of a 1 in 750 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 447,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 1000 ml of a 1 in 1250 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 448,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 200 ml of a 1 in 2500 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 449,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 120 ml of a 1 in 2400 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 450,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 330 ml of a 1 in 2200 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 451,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 500 ml of a 1 in 1750 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 452,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 440 ml of a 1 in 1650 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 453,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 120 ml of a 1 in 200 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 454,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 210 ml of a 1 in 350 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 455,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 550 ml of a 1 in 1925 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 456,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 490 ml of a 1 in 1750 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 457,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 400 ml of a 1 in 375 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 458,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 150 ml of a 1 in 525 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 459,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 640 ml of a 1 in 200 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 460,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 75 solution should be taken to make 240 ml of a 1 in 225 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 461,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 800 ml of a 1 in 400 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 462,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 500 ml of a 1 in 750 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 463,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 225 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 464,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 660 ml of a 1 in 1375 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 465,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 400 ml of a 1 in 400 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 466,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 160 ml of a 1 in 400 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 467,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 720 ml of a 1 in 1800 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 468,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 60 ml of a 1 in 1350 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 469,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 160 ml of a 1 in 300 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 470,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 660 ml of a 1 in 1650 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 471,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 200 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 472,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 1800 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 473,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 900 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 474,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 70 ml of a 1 in 1225 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 475,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 660 ml of a 1 in 1925 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 476,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 300 ml of a 1 in 875 solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 477,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 480 ml of a 1 in 300 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 478,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 160 ml of a 1 in 300 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 479,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 300 ml of a 1 in 1350 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 480,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 600 ml of a 1 in 150 solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 481,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 250 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 482,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 420 ml of a 1 in 600 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 483,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 2025 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 484,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 100 solution should be taken to make 500 ml of a 1 in 1000 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 485,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 160 ml of a 1 in 200 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 486,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 140 ml of a 1 in 350 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 487,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 150 solution should be taken to make 900 ml of a 1 in 1500 solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 488,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 360 ml of a 1 in 450 solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 489,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 30 ml of a 1 in 375 solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 490,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 125 solution should be taken to make 500 ml of a 1 in 1250 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 491,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 300 ml of a 1 in 1750 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 492,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 175 solution should be taken to make 300 ml of a 1 in 1750 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 493,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 320 ml of a 1 in 900 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 494,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 120 ml of a 1 in 1200 solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 495,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 200 ml of a 1 in 800 solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 496,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 200 solution should be taken to make 280 ml of a 1 in 800 solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 497,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 50 solution should be taken to make 90 ml of a 1 in 150 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 498,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 180 ml of a 1 in 1350 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 499,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 25 solution should be taken to make 400 ml of a 1 in 125 solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 500,
    "Question": "How many ml of a 1 in 225 solution should be taken to make 330 ml of a 1 in 2475 solution?",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "ml"
  }
]
